你瞅瞅 Raj都崩溃了
You hear that? Raj is devastated.
Sheldon 嘘 婚礼开始了
Sheldon, shh. The wedding's starting.
我知道怎么回事了
I see what's happening.
大家要分裂成小团体了
Sides are forming.
假如Bernadette站在Amy那边 那我就选Howard
Well, if Bernadette's on Amy's team, I pick Howard.
我保持中立
I'm not taking sides.
好吧 那我只好选Raj了
Fine, I guess I'm stuck with Raj.
是吗?
Really?
至少有人选你呢
At least you got picked.
我提前问一句
Before I go any further,
你们双方都准备好婚礼誓词了吗?
have either of you prepared your own vows?
- 准备了  - 没有
- Yes.  - No.
你写了誓词?
You wrote vows?
对啊
Yeah.
我还没有呢
Well, I don't have any.
你这是让我出洋相啊
You're kind of making me look bad.
没事的 我... 我也没必要念出来
It's okay. I... I don't have to say them.
不 不 不 念吧
No, no, no, go ahead.
我能想点煽情的 然后你会哭 一切都搞定
I'll come up with something mushy, you'll cry, we got this.
"Penny 我们是由
"Penny, we are made of particles
"宇宙形成时就存在的粒子组成的
"That have existed since the moment the universe began.